smileyswelove.com 2013-04-23

# Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

Originally Posted January 5th, 2013 | Last reviewed: January 5th, 2013 

This site uses Google AdSense for 3rd party advertising. [Link to Google Policies and Principles](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/)  
This site uses Janrain for social login. [Link to the Janrain Privacy Policy](http://janrain.com/janrain-privacy-policy/)

### What information we collect

When you visit our website, we utilize various google services. Please read the link above for details on what Google collects. 

Our Terms of Use further specifies conditions for the use of the extension in the Chrome browser. 

#### Voluntary Sharing

You may choose to sign up for a SmileysWeLove account using a social network login, such as Facebook, Yahoo, Google, etc. For that purpose, we use Janrain to handle the login, and Janrain will store necesarry data to identify you on subsequent logins. A link to the Janrain privacy policy is listed above. 

When you sign up, we store the following information on our servers to supply you with the best experience possible: 

  * Unique Janrain identifier
  * Your name, if shared via social login
  * Your email, if shared via social login
  * Your username
  * Your URL, if shared via social login
  * Your avatar photo, if shared via social login
  * The time of your last login

### Use of Information

While using our services, we store information about your uploaded images, and smileys you've used, etc, in order to customize your experience. 

We do not sell your information. 

### Use of Cookies and Log File technologies

Cookies are a standard Internet technology, and many major web sites use them to provide useful features for their members. Cookies allow us to store and retrieve login information on a user's system. They provide us with data that we can use to improve the quality of our service and make it easier to use. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you'd prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies. However, you may not be able to take full advantage of SmileysWeLove.com if you do so. 

As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. 

We use this information, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. 

We do not link automatically-collected data through the use of cookies and log files to personally identifiable information. 

### Aquisition

We reserve the right to transfer your personal information in the event of a transfer of ownership of SqueakyChocolate, LLC., such as acquisition by or merger with another company. If an acquiring company should plan to materially change this privacy policy, we will notify you beforehand. 

### Security

The security of your personal information depends on your protection of your account. Please do not disclose your login credentials to unauthorized people. We use industry standard technology designed to help keep your personal information safe. If you have any other questions about the security of our website, please contact us at privacy@smileyswelove.com. 

### Changes in Privacy Policy

From time to time we may update this Privacy Policy and will post a notice of any significant changes on our website. You should visit this page periodically to review any such changes to the privacy policy. Your continued use of this website or our service and/or continued provision of personally identifiable information to us will be subject to the terms of the then-current Privacy Policy. 

### How to Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns about SmileysWeLove.com's Privacy Policy or its implementation, you may contact us at this email address: privacy@smileyswelove.com
